let questions = [
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",
    options: [
      "if (condition):",
      "if condition",
      "if: condition",
      "if condition:",
    ],
    answer: "if condition:",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",
    options: ["String", "Number", "Boolean", "ArrayList"],
    answer: "ArrayList",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",
    options: ["var", "let", "const", "int"],
    answer: "int",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",
    options: [
      "for i = 0 to 10",
      "for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",
      "for (int i = 0; i <= 10)",
      "for i in range(0, 10)",
    ],
    answer: "for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",
    options: ["while", "for", "do-while", "foreach"],
    answer: "foreach",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",
    options: ["+", "-", "*", "$"],
    answer: "$",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question:
      "In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",
    options: ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "C++"],
    answer: "Python",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",
    options: ["function name()", "def name", "function name", "def name()"],
    answer: "def name()",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",
    options: ["Int", "String", "Double", "Object"],
    answer: "Object",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",
    options: ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "C++"],
    answer: "C++",
    category: "coding",
  },
];
